<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CS2 Weapons</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="type">Type</string>
    <string name="purchasable_by">Purchasable By</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="price">Price</string>
    <string name="damage">Damage</string>
    <string name="m_hanief_fatkhan_nashrullah">M. Hanief Fatkhan Nashrullah</string>
    <string name="hanief23fatkhan_gmail_com">hanief23fatkhan@gmail.com</string>

    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>AK-47</item>
        <item>AWP</item>
        <item>M4A4</item>
        <item>M4A1-S</item>
        <item>Desert Eagle</item>
        <item>USP-S</item>
        <item>Glock-18</item>
        <item>Galil AR</item>
        <item>MP9</item>
        <item>MAC-10</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_price">
        <item>$2700</item>
        <item>$4750</item>
        <item>$2900</item>
        <item>$2900</item>
        <item>$700</item>
        <item>$200</item>
        <item>$200</item>
        <item>$1800</item>
        <item>$1250</item>
        <item>$1050</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_damage">
        <item>36</item>
        <item>115</item>
        <item>33</item>
        <item>38</item>
        <item>53</item>
        <item>35</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>26</item>
        <item>29</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_type">
        <item>Rifle</item>
        <item>Sniper Rifle</item>
        <item>Rifle</item>
        <item>Rifle</item>
        <item>Pistol</item>
        <item>Pistol</item>
        <item>Pistol</item>
        <item>Rifle</item>
        <item>SMG</item>
        <item>SMG</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_purchasable_by">
        <item>T</item>
        <item>CT &amp; T</item>
        <item>CT</item>
        <item>CT</item>
        <item>CT &amp; T</item>
        <item>CT</item>
        <item>T</item>
        <item>T</item>
        <item>CT</item>
        <item>T</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>The AK–47 is a select–fire, gas-operated 7.62×39mm assault rifle developed in the Soviet Union by Mikhail Kalashnikov. The first weapon in the AK (Avtomat Kalashnikova, Russian: Автомат Калашникова, Kalashnikov assault rifle) family of weapons, the AK-47 is succeeded by the modernized AKM in 1959, and the AK-74 in 1974. AK variants were adopted by many forces around the world and saw use in almost every conflict since its development. The AK-47 in Global Offensive is modeled after the AKMN, a variant of the AKM which can attach Warsaw Pact optics to its dovetail mount.\n\nIn-game, the AK-47 is a powerful assault rifle exclusive to the Terrorists. It is one of the most popular and efficient guns in the game known for its power, range, and cheap price. The AK-47 can kill a helmeted player with one shot to the head, something which its CT counterparts (Maverick M4A1 Carbine, M4A4, and M4A1-S) cannot do. Even without headshots, it is able to bring down an enemy in 4 Chest &amp; Arm shots instead of 5 with the CT counterparts. It has high first shot accuracy and low damage dropoff, and a moderately fast reload. In Global Offensive, the first 8-9 bullets in its spray pattern have little to no side to side recoil, making compensation somewhat simple.\n\nThe AK-47\'s only major disadvantages are its inaccuracy after multiple shots and high recoil. In Global Offensive, the upwards recoil in the first few shots of its spray pattern is quite strong, requiring more mouse movement to compensate. After that, the recoil moves to strong side-to-side sway, which is harder to compensate. Its CT counterparts are easier to control in this regard. Its rate of fire is lower than its CT counterparts, and is also fairly heavy, slowing down the player more. It is also one of the loudest rifles and has a very distinctive firing noise, allowing enemies to easily identify users of the AK-47. </item>
        <item>The Accuracy International Arctic Warfare series is a series of sniper rifles manufactured by Accuracy International of United Kingdom. The Arctic Warfare Police (AWP) is the law enforcement variant of the series, commonly chambered for 7.62×51mm NATO. The Magnum Sniper Rifle depicted in Counter-Strike is based on the Arctic Warfare Magnum, chambered for .338 Lapua Magnum. The AWP in Global Offensive is based off the original Arctic Warfare.\n\nIn-game, the AWP is a high-powered bolt-action sniper rifle available to both teams, with a 5-round magazine capacity in Counter-Strike 2 and Global Offensive whereas in earlier games it has a 10-round magazine. The AWP is not available for the Counter-Terrorists to purchase in Assassination maps. They can, however, get them from fallen Terrorists.\n\nIt is a devastatingly powerful long-range weapon, with extreme accuracy and obscene stopping power. However, its high price tag and cumbersome playstyle requires massive amounts of training, practice, accuracy and experience to master its usage.\n\nWhen not scoped in, the rifle is very inaccurate and has no crosshair to assist aiming. The scope can be used with secondary fire which makes an audible sound to everyone when activating it, and pressing secondary fire again while scoped in zooms in the scope. The player\'s movement speed is reduced while scoped in. Firing the weapon causes the player to leave the scope temporarily to operate the bolt before automatically scoping in again. The player will leave the scope if they use secondary fire again at the higher zoom setting or switches weapons. When using the scope and not moving, the rifle has a near-perfect accuracy, able to hit anything as long as the crosshair of the scope is on target. Running or walking drastically reduces accuracy, and even more so with jumping whereas crouch walking maintains its accuracy.\n\nIt boasts an exceedingly high damage value, and is a source of much of its infamy. It is able to one-shot kill enemies with one hit to anywhere bar the legs, regardless of armor. The VIP and Lab Rat are the only player characters who can survive a single body shot from the AWP because his armor can absorb 200 damage. In the case of the Lab Rat, he can take the whole damage due to the increased health (to 120 HP) in Danger Zone. However, a headshot can still kill both of the above players instantly. It also has a very high penetration power, and its high base damage makes it a solid weapon for wallbanging.\n\nHowever, where the AWP excels in accuracy and power, it suffers in general handling. The weapon has terrible accuracy when not using the scope or firing while running or walking, so the user must be using the scope at all times to remain competitive. Because the weapon is bolt-action, it also results in a very low rate of fire. The AWP slows players down considerably, particularly in Global Offensive, making it unwieldy at closer ranges. It is also less accurate if fired right after cycling the bolt in Source and Global Offensive, and has a moderately long reload time in these games.The last major downside is the weapon\'s very expensive price tag, one of the most expensive in the game. In older games, the .338 Lapua Magnum used by the AWP is the also most expensive ammunition in-game, at $125 per magazine. In addition, it has a reduced kill reward in Global Offensive, further hampering the economic ability of the team using it. Enormous quantities of skill and team coordination are needed to use the AWP effectively, so its user doesn\'t become an economic load and drag down the whole team, or even getting killed and letting the enemy claim a free AWP. \n\nAdditionally, the AWP\'s sound signature is extremely loud and distinct when fired, making it easy for enemy players to single out an AWP player in the vicinity and change tactics accordingly. </item>
        <item>The M4A4 is based on the Mk 18 Mod 0 carbine, fitted with an ARMS#40 flip-up rear iron sight and KAC free-float RAS handguard with rail covers. This rifle is derived from the standard M4A1, but uses a different upper receiver (known as the Close Quarters Battle Receiver). This allows for the use of a shorter barrel - very useful for fighting in tight spaces.\n\nIn-game, the weapon holds 30 rounds and has 90 rounds in reserve. </item>
        <item>The M4A1-S is the reintroduction of the original M4A1 from earlier Counter-Strike games, originally replaced by the M4A4 in Global Offensive. The M4A1-S in game is based off a Colt Model 723 \"M16A2 Carbine\" (an early predecessor to the M4 Carbine identified by the non-removable carry handle) with an \"M4\" profile barrel.\n\nIn game, the weapon\'s capacity and reserve capacity is reduced compared to its predecessor, at 20 rounds per magazine and 80 rounds in reserve, which is the lowest out of all assault rifles. Its rate of fire is slightly lowered at 600 RPM, slightly lower than the average assault rifle fire-rate or 667.\n\nThe M4A1-S is equipped with a silencer, which is attached when receiving the weapon, and can be manually detached (and reattached) by pressing the secondary fire key. The time taken for detaching and reattaching the silencer is greatly increased, so it is unadvised to do it in the midst of combat.\n\nThe silencer is best kept on because removing it increases recoil and decreases accuracy, making it less effective overall than its non-silenced counterpart M4A4. One reason to do so however is that the silencer noticeably increases the length of the weapon, which may make stealth around corners slightly more difficult.\n\nWith the silencer on, the weapon has a quiet firing sound, low recoil, and high accuracy. It also doesn\'t fire tracers. These properties make the M4A1-S suitable for long-range tapfiring.\n\nThe max audible distance of silenced firing sound the M4A1-S is 800 units</item>
        <item>The IMI Desert Eagle is a large semi-automatic pistol chambering the powerful .50 Action Express round, one of the most powerful pistol cartridges in production. It was designed by Magnum Research Inc. of the United States, which was refined and manufactured by Israel Military Industries (save for a temporary contract with Saco Defense from 1995 to 1998) until 2009 when production moved to MRI\'s own facility in the United States. While not practical for military use due to its size and recoil, its large, powerful appearance made it a popular choice for movies and games.\n\nIn-game, the Desert Eagle is a powerful semi-automatic pistol available to both teams. It is loaded with 7 rounds of .50 Action Express which makes it able to inflict high amounts of damage. It costs $650 in earlier games and $700 in Global Offensive.\n\nThe Desert Eagle is one of the more popular sidearms in the Counter-Strike games, its appeal mainly coming from its high power. Until Global Offensive, this pistol was the only pistol capable of killing an opponent with one headshot regardless of armor and helmet. In Global Offensive, while other pistols can also achieve this feat, the Desert Eagle has far better range than most of them, with high base damage that can compensate for damage dropoff at range and a far better standing accuracy than most other pistols. In Global Offensive, the Desert Eagle is also the only weapon in the pistol class with high penetration.\n\nThe Desert Eagle\'s main disadvantages come from its small magazine size, lower rate of fire, high recoil when fired repeatedly, low movement speed when wielding the weapon (it is the second heaviest pistol in Global Offensive, only beaten by R8 Revolver), and price (it is the most expensive pistol in Global Offensive, but is beaten out by the Five-SeveN and Dual Berettas in earlier games). Damage dropoff is also quite strong, though not as noticeable due to its high base damage. Its firing sound is loud and distinctive, meaning that it can give the player\'s position away easily. </item>
        <item>The USP (Universale Selbstladepistole or \"universal self-loading pistol\") is a semi-automatic pistol developed in Germany by Heckler &amp; Koch GmbH (H&amp;K) of Oberndorf am Neckar as a replacement for the P7 series of handguns. In Counter-Strike: Global Offensive, like its predecessor, the USP pistol is the USP Tactical variant of the default USP. The -S represents the silencer.\n\nThe pistol is an alternative option to the P2000, making it one of the Counter-Terrorists\'s spawn pistols. If equipped in the inventory menu before the match, a CT player will receive an USP-S at the start of a round if any of the following happen: it is the first round in a half; they died in the last round; or if they ended the last round without a sidearm (eg dropped it). If Counter Terrorist players drop the pistol at the start of a round, they may also repurchase one from the buy menu for $200.\n\nThe USP-S was released in the Arms Deal update that brought the M4A1-S, which also features a suppressor. Both weapons are reintroductions of weapons from previous Counter-Strike games which were removed at the start of Global Offensive. In this case, the USP-S is a counterpart to the original P2000.\n\nThe USP-S has a silencer which is equipped by default when receiving the weapon, although using the secondary fire key players can detach and reattach it at will. The silencer is best kept on because removing it increases recoil and decreases accuracy, making it overall less effective than the non-silenced choice, the P2000. One reason to remove the silencer is that it noticeably decreases the length of the weapon, which may make stealth around corners slightly easier.\n\nWith the silencer on, the USP-S has high accuracy and moderate recoil. It also has a high running accuracy, but low magazine capacity and reserve ammunition capacity, and a low rate of fire. Its damage is respectable but its armor penetration is low, making it good for long-range pistol round combat but less than ideal for later rounds.\n\nThe max audible distance of silenced firing sound the USP-S is 800 units.</item>
        <item>The Glock 18 is a selective-fire variant of the Glock 17, developed at the request of the Austrian Counter-Terrorist unit EKO Cobra. This machine pistol has a lever-type fire-control selector switch, installed on the serrated portion of the rear left side of the slide. With the selector lever in the bottom position, the pistol will fire fully automatic and, with the selector lever in the top position, the pistol will fire semi-automatically. Because of its design as a machine pistol, in real life, it is exclusively used by counter-terrorism operatives and is not available to the general public in most countries.\n\nIn-game, the Glock-18 is the spawn pistol for the Terrorist team. A T player will receive a Glock at the start of a round if it is the first round in a half, they died in the last round, or if they ended the last round without a sidearm.\n\nIf players wish, they may also purchase one from the buy menu. It is available to both teams\' buy menu in earlier games and in Global Offensive before the January 23, 2013 update, but has since been restricted to the Terrorists\' buy menu only. It is one of the cheapest firearms in the Counter-Strike series, costing only $200 in Global Offensive (the others being the P2000 and USP-S) and $400 in the previous games.\n\nWhile GoldSrc versions of the Glock-18 maintain a faithful resemblance to the real pistol, the version in Source more closely resembles the Glock 19, the compact version of the Glock 17. The depiction in Global Offensive, based on the Glock pistol from Left 4 Dead 2, closely resembles a Glock 26, but the slide and frame have been extended to the length of the Glock 17.\n\nUnlike the real Glock-18, the in-game portrayal of the Glock-18 features a selector switch and a burst-fire mode in place of the automatic mode. It is one of two weapons in Counter-Strike with a burst mode, the other being the FAMAS. The player spawns with the pistol in semi-automatic mode, and can switch to the burst mode with the alternate fire key, and can switch back to semi-automatic fire by using the alternate fire key again. In Global Offensive, switching the fire mode makes a distinctive \"click\" noise audible to all players.\n\nBurst-fire offers a much higher rate of fire, allowing for a higher burst damage, at the cost of longer delays in between bursts and less controllable recoil and inaccuracy. It is recommended to use semi-automatic mode for medium to long ranges and burst mode for short-range.\n\nCompared to other pistols, the Glock-18 has inferior firepower and poor armor penetration in GoldSrc games. Don\'t be fooled by the fact that it doesn\'t have any visual recoil, it has innacuracy from firing on GoldSrc games. It is common for the Glock to be discarded in favor of better pistols. Despite its massive flaws, its advantages are its magazine size (20 rounds, second largest for pistols only losing to Dual Berettas), low recoil, high rate of fire, and good accuracy in all games. As a pistol, it is also lightweight and has a short reload time. These advantages come to light in pistol rounds, where players need to conserve money and many players go without armor, helmet, and more advanced weapons. The Glock\'s high rate of fire and burst mode makes it effective for rushing and thus is a good counterbalance for the CTs\' accuracy oriented spawn pistols (USP/USP-S/P2000). The Glock appears to be effective at close range against unarmored opponents.\n\nAlongside with the FAMAS, bots will never use the burst-fire of the Glock, preferring the semi-automatic mode instead.\n\nEven if the player has set the Glock to fire in burst-mode, it can only fire semi-automatically when combined with the tactical shield.\n\nIf equipped with the K&amp;M Sub-Machine Gun or Schmidt Machine Pistol, the Glock will share an ammo pool of 120 rounds with them. This is because all three weapons use 9mm Parabellum ammunition, but ammo is shared only in GoldSrc Counter-Strike games. In Counter-Strike: Source and Counter-Strike: Global Offensive, all types of ammo sharing had been removed.</item>
        <item>The Galil AR is modeled after the Galil ACE 22, an Israeli assault rifle manufactured by Israel Weapon Industries. The ACE 22 is the medium barrel version of the IWI Galil ACE series, produced since 2008. Its in-game name comes from a different weapon in the same family, the Galil AR.\n\nIn-game, the Galil AR costs $1800, making it the cheapest Terrorist assault rifle. It has a high rate of fire but moderately strong recoil. It holds 35 rounds in its magazine, 5 more than most other assault rifles, and has a good penetration power. Its primary disadvantage is that it cannot instantly kill targets at full health and armor with a single headshot, and accuracy is somewhat low at long range.\n\nIn general, the Galil AR is a good choice for an eco round assault rifle, but is not very good for buy rounds. </item>
        <item>The MP9 is a 9mm machine pistol manufactured by Switzerland-based Brügger &amp; Thomet AG, and is a development of the Steyr TMP (Brügger &amp; Thomet purchased the design rights from Steyr in 2001). Differences from the TMP include a new Picatinny rail for attachments, a right-side folding stock, and a new safety trigger.\n\nIn-game, the MP9 is a cheap SMG available to the CTs. It boasts a high rate of fire, fast movement speed, and swift reload time. It also has very impressive accuracy statistics across, particularly when moving and jumping, with its jumping accuracy being the highest of all SMGs and even higher than its running accuracy. This makes the MP9 one of the better \"spray \'n\' pray\" weapons. Its damage dropoff is surprisingly the lowest out of all SMGs.\n\nHowever, the MP9 suffers from high recoil, low damage, and low penetration power, making the weapon favoured in anti-eco rounds (where it can achieve one-hit headshot kills against unarmored opponents) but always swapped out for rifles or the P90.\n\nAs with most other SMGs in CS:GO, the MP9 awards twice the money for a kill compared to most weapons ($600 in Competitive Mode, $300 in Casual Mode). </item>
        <item>The MAC-10 (Military Armament Corporation Model 10, officially the M-10) is a compact, blowback operated machine pistol developed by Gordon B. Ingram in 1964. It can be chambered in either .45 ACP or 9mm rounds. It is chambered in .45 ACP in-game.\n\nIn-game, the MAC-10 is a moderately powerful machine pistol available to only the Terrorists. It has a very high rate of fire and medium damage, and is a relatively cheap option ($1400 in earlier games and $1050 in Global Offensive).\n\nThe major disadvantages are its high damage dropoff (though its higher base damage compensates for it somewhat), bad accuracy (though moving inaccuracy is relatively low) and high recoil, which is mostly horizontal. Its armor penetration is also weak, making it unsuitable for later rounds. For those reasons, the MAC-10 is very uncommon and very rarely seen during public or competitive play.\n\nThe weapon is very light and allows for a high movement speed. The MAC-10\'s reload time is somewhat long before Global Offensive, but is significantly shortened in Global Offensive.\n\nIn Global Offensive, the MAC-10 has an increased kill reward ($600) due to being a sub-machinegun.\n\nPrior to Global Offensive, if equipped at the same time with the K&amp;M .45 Tactical, the two will share an ammo pool of 100 rounds as they share the same cartridge</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/ak47</item>
        <item>@drawable/awp</item>
        <item>@drawable/m4a4</item>
        <item>@drawable/m4a1s</item>
        <item>@drawable/deagle</item>
        <item>@drawable/usps</item>
        <item>@drawable/glock18</item>
        <item>@drawable/galilar</item>
        <item>@drawable/mp9</item>
        <item>@drawable/mac10</item>
    </integer-array>

</resources>